Sebastian Soto

Software Developer

Details

(+506) 8667-2549

s.m.sebastian.n@gmail.com sebastian-nsm.herokuapp.com

About Me

Freelance software developer with experience using a variety of technologies. Passionate about automation and making life easier and enhancing the everyday life experience through the use of technology. An experienced team player, able to adapt to the needs of the company or team. Also, a firm believer that communication is key for success on every project.

Web Developer at Advisory & Management Services, San José

Skills

C#

Employment History

C++

lava

Nov 2019 - Present

JavaFX

Web Developer at Arru Foundation, Cartago

Undergraduate at Cenfotec, San José

Android

Dec 2019 - Present

Education

May 2018 - Present

Python

Flask

HTML

CSS

SASS

Bootstrap 4

JavaScript

Node.js

Firebase

Transact-SQL

PL / SQL

Courses

Introduction to Java Programming: Starting to Code in Java,

UC3M

Jan 2018 - Feb 2018

The Complete Android 8.0 Oreo Developer Course, Udemy

Feb 2018 - Mar 2018

Languages

Spanish

English

The Complete Android & Java Bootcamp - Material Design

UI/UX, Udemy

Feb 2018 - Apr 2018

Hobbies

Playing basketball and volleyball, listening to music, playing the saxophone, video games, movies, and learning

Zuraye Badilla **Vargas**

William Allen Taylor Turrialba Hospital and Blood Bank (+506) 2556-8683 zbadillav@yahoo.es

References

Elizabeth Escalante Barquero

LLM Law Firm (+506) 8860-6456 eescalante@llm.co.cr

Noé Soto Pérez

Advisory & **Management Services** (+506) 8873-3614 noe.soto@ams-cr.com